[
  {
    "front": "simple table",
    "back": "&ltp&gtSimple table&lt/p&gt &lttable&gt  &lttr&gt   &lttd&gtJohn&lt/td&gt   &lttd&gtDoe&lt/td&gt  &lt/tr&gt  &lttr&gt   &lttd&gtJane&lt/td&gt   &lttd&gtDoe&lt/td&gt  &lt/tr&gt &lt/table&gt"
  },
  {
    "front": "Simple table with header",
    "back": "&ltp&gtSimple table with header&lt/p&gt &lttable&gt  &lttr&gt   &ltth&gtFirst name&lt/th&gt   &ltth&gtLast name&lt/th&gt  &lt/tr&gt  &lttr&gt   &lttd&gtJohn&lt/td&gt   &lttd&gtDoe&lt/td&gt  &lt/tr&gt  &lttr&gt   &lttd&gtJane&lt/td&gt   &lttd&gtDoe&lt/td&gt  &lt/tr&gt &lt/table&gt"
  },
  {
    "front": "Table with thead, tfoot, and tbody",
    "back": "&ltp&gtTable with thead, tfoot, and tbody&lt/p&gt &lttable&gt  &ltthead&gt   &lttr&gt    &ltth&gtHeader content 1&lt/th&gt    &ltth&gtHeader content 2&lt/th&gt   &lt/tr&gt  &lt/thead&gt  &lttfoot&gt   &lttr&gt    &lttd&gtFooter content 1&lt/td&gt    &lttd&gtFooter content 2&lt/td&gt   &lt/tr&gt  &lt/tfoot&gt  &lttbody&gt   &lttr&gt    &lttd&gtBody content 1&lt/td&gt    &lttd&gtBody content 2&lt/td&gt   &lt/tr&gt  &lt/tbody&gt &lt/table&gt"
  },
  {
    "front": "A basic input box",
    "back": "&lt!-- A basic input --&gt &ltinput type=\"text\" name=\"input\" value=\"Type here\"&gt"
  },
  {
    "front": "password box",
    "back": "&ltinput type=\"password\" name=\"pwd\"&gt"
  },
  {
    "front": "radio buttons",
    "back": "&ltform&gt &ltinput type=\"radio\" name=\"sex\" value=\"male\"&gtMale&ltbr&gt &ltinput type=\"radio\" name=\"sex\" value=\"female\"&gtFemale &lt/form&gt"
  },
  {
    "front": "checkboxes",
    "back": "&ltform&gt &ltinput type=\"checkbox\" name=\"vehicle\" value=\"Bike\"&gtI have a bike&ltbr&gt &ltinput type=\"checkbox\" name=\"vehicle\" value=\"Car\"&gtI have a car &lt/form&gt"
  },
  {
    "front": "simple form with submit button",
    "back": "&lt!-- Simple form which will send a GET request --&gt &ltform action=\"\"&gt  &ltlabel for=\"GET-name\"&gtName:&lt/label&gt  &ltinput id=\"GET-name\" type=\"text\" name=\"name\"&gt  &ltinput type=\"submit\" value=\"Save\"&gt &lt/form&gt  &lt!-- Simple form which will send a POST request --&gt &ltform action=\"\" method=\"post\"&gt  &ltlabel for=\"POST-name\"&gtName:&lt/label&gt  &ltinput id=\"POST-name\" type=\"text\" name=\"name\"&gt  &ltinput type=\"submit\" value=\"Save\"&gt &lt/form&gt"
  },
  {
    "front": "drop-down list",
    "back": "&lt!-- The second value will be selected initially --&gt &ltselect name=\"select\"&gt  &ltoption value=\"value1\"&gtValue 1&lt/option&gt  &ltoption value=\"value2\" selected&gtValue 2&lt/option&gt  &ltoption value=\"value3\"&gtValue 3&lt/option&gt &lt/select&gt"
  },
  {
    "front": "input checked events",
    "back": "/* any \"checkable\" element */ :checked {   width: 50px;   height: 50px; }  /* only radio elements */   input[type=\"radio\"]:checked {   margin-left: 25px; }  /* only checkbox elements */ input[type=\"checkbox\"]:checked {   display: none; }  /* only option elements */ option:checked {   color: red; }"
  },
  {
    "front": "label with for attribute",
    "back": "&lt!-- Simple label example with for attribute --&gt &ltlabel for=\"Name\"&gtClick me&lt/label&gt &ltinput type=\"text\" id=\"Name\" name=\"Name\" /&gt  &lt!-- or more simply --&gt &ltlabel&gtClick me &ltinput type=\"text\" id=\"Name\" name=\"Name\" /&gt&lt/label&gt"
  }
]
